privateschooljewel.com 2018-09-11

# Private School Jewel

## **Our Commitment to Privacy**

Private School Jewel values our customers and respects your privacy. This privacy policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use and protect it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. By providing your personal information to Private School Jewel, you are consenting to the manner in which we collect, use, disclose, protect and otherwise manage that information.

If our information practices change, we will post an updated version of the policy on our website. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our website and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. Your continued use of our website constitutes your consent to be bound by the revised policy.

You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this policy at any time. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us as described in the section below entitled **How Do I Contact You?** �

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**What kind of personal information does Private School Jewel collect?**  
We do not collect or hold credit card information. We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, or credit card number when you visit our website. We may save your information with us online, contact you with a question or concern, or ask you to participate in a contest, promotion, or survey. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online. We may combine all of this information with information about you that we acquire from our joint marketing partners and from unrelated third parties.

**How does Private School Jewel use my personal information?**  
We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * To process and fulfill your order, including sending you emails to confirm your order status and shipment
  * To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications
  * To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions
  * To help us learn more about your shopping preferences
  * To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services
  * To enhance your shopping experience in online
  * To analyze trends and statistics
  * To protect the security or integrity of our website and our business
  * To contact you if necessary
  * To facilitate social sharing functionality

**Does Private School Jewel share my personal information?**  
We may share your personal information in the following ways:

  * We may share your information with our service providers who manage our customer information and perform services on our behalf, such as fulfilling promotions, sending communications to our customers, conducting surveys, etc. We do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use or disclosure of your information.
  * We may share your information when we team up with another company to jointly offer or provide products, services, contests, or promotions to our customers.
  * We may share your information to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of Private School Jewel or others.

In addition, if you choose to participate in any third-party scrip, loyalty, or similar program in which a Private School Jewel brand is a participating vendor, and you authorize Private School Jewel or our credit card processor to provide information about your purchases to the organization administering the program, we will share your personal information with that program.

In the unlikely event of a sale or merger of Private School Jewel or any of our businesses, assets or brands, our customers� personal information and other information we have collected as described in this policy may be among the transferred business assets.

**How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?**  
Private School Jewel wants to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information, such as information about special offers and sales events, from one or more of our brands, you can let us know by contacting our customer service as described in the section below entitled, �How Do I Contact You?�

Please be sure to include your full name and the email address you used when you made a purchase from the Private School Jewel brand. If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a �do not contact� file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from Private School Jewel.

Please note that when you make an online purchase from us, we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order.

**How does Private School Jewel protect kids� privacy?**  
Private School Jewel is concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request or collect personal information online from anyone under the age of 18. Our website is a mature audience site and is not targeted to or intended for use by children. If you are a parent and believe we may have inadvertently collected such information from your child, please notify us immediately by sending an e-mail to [bratcash@gmail.com](mailto:%20bratcash@gmail.com) **** ****

**Third Party Ads**  
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Please note that these companies may use information about your visit to this website and third-party websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this website, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**OTHER INFORMATION**

**Other Information We Collect**

Other Information is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to you as an individual, such as browser information, information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies, demographic information and other information provided by you or aggregated information.

**How Does Private School Jewel Collect Other Information?**  
We and our third party service providers may collect Other Information through your browser: Certain information is collected by most browsers, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system version and Internet browser type and version. We use this information to ensure that our website functions properly.

When you visit the Private School Jewel website, we collect information to improve the content of our website for marketing and promotional purposes. Each time you visit our website, our web server automatically recognizes your IP address, monitor resolution and what type of browser you are using. We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, and collect customer information gathered in the course of joining our online member base and/or processing sales transactions.

**IMPORTANT INFORMATION**

**What about links to other websites?**  
For your convenience and information, our website may contain links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our website.

**How do I contact you?**  
For questions about our privacy policy, to make choices about receiving promotional communications, to update your personal information, or to place an order, you can contact Private School Jewel by email:

**How do I know my personal information is secure?**  
We take precautions, including the use of encryption technologies and authentication tools, to protect the security of your personal information and to provide you with a safe and convenient shopping experience. We have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personal information.

When you enter your personal information on our website, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from �http� to �https.�

Some browsers and firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you will be unable to connect to our server so you will not have to worry about mistakenly placing an order through an unsecured connection. If you can�t access the server, you can place your order by email [bratcash@gmail.com](mailto:%20bratcash@gmail.com) **** ****

THANK YOU
